yaspan.com 2015-04-08

# Privacy, Terms, Conditions and Copyright

**Privacy, Terms, Conditions and Copyright Policy of yaspan.com, LLC.  
**   
yaspan.com takes your privacy seriously. Our privacy policy is designed to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of the information we collect. We encourage you to read our full privacy policy, below:   
**  
Information Collected**  
yaspan.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about individuals, except when such information is voluntarily submitted by the user.  
In common with many websites, yaspan.com automatically logs certain non-personally identifiable information about visits to our websites. This information is used for system administration and for producing usage statistics.  
We do collect email addresses from individuals that wish to take advantage of special promotional offers, but we do not sell, rent or disclose collected email addresses to third parties.

**Cookies**  
As you browse yaspan.com sites, we place "cookies" on your hard drive to show which source (search engine and keywords, newsletter or site notification, pay-per-click ad and so on) you used to find our site. We do not use cookies to track single-user data.  

**Opt-Out Policy**  
yaspan.com gives users options to opt out wherever practical; such choices include:  
• Opting not to receive our electronic newsletters when registering for a site  
• Opting not to receive review site notifications  

**Unsubscribe Policy**  
Users may unsubscribe from any of our electronic newsletters or site notifications at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of each newsletter or notification.  

**Use of Collected Information**  
Collecting the information described above enables us to tailor our content to our readers' needs.

**Third Party Partners**  
yaspan.com has teamed up with reputable third party vendors in order to provide certain services to its online users. When leaving our website to view one of our partner websites, we encourage users to review the privacy statements of those websites as we cannot guarantee the privacy of users while visiting affiliate sites. yaspan.com may use third-party companies to serve ads or analyze behavior patterns when you visit our Web site. These companies may place or provide ads (such as banner ads) on this Web site that might also place cookies. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our Web site in order to help us improve our user experience and/or provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of providing these services or placing these ads, these third-party companies may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your computer and each of these companies uses this cookie information according to their own privacy and security policies.   

**Use of This Site**  
As a reader or user of yaspan.com, you are using the site as a privilege, not a right, free of charge. Therefore the owner and operators of this site may, at any time, at their discretion, disable/ban your user account or prevent your use of this site. 

**Indemnity**  
You will indemnify and hold harmless yaspan.com, its parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, customers, vendors, officers and employees from any liability, damage or cost (including reasonable attorneys. fees and cost) from any claim or demand made by any third party or yourself, due to or arising out of your access to the Site, use of the Services, violation of the Terms of Use by you, or the infringement by you, or any third party using your account or yaspan.com User ID, or of any intellectual property or other right of any person or entity. 

**Acceptance of Terms**  
By using the yaspan.com website, you signify your acceptance of this website privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. Your continued use of any yaspan.com site following the posting of changes to these terms will indicate your acceptance of those changes.

If you have questions about our privacy or legal policies, contact the Editor In Chief via email:  

 **Copyright Policy:**  
We respect the intellectual property and copyright of others. As such, we have a policy of removing user submissions that violate copyright law, suspending access to our services and to any user who uses the services in violation of copyright law, as well as terminating, in appropriate circumstances, the account of any user who uses our services in violation of copyright law. 

Pursuant to Title 17 of the United States Code, Section 512, we have implemented procedures for receiving written notification of claimed copyright infringement and for processing claims in accordance with the law. If you believe a user of yaspan.com's service is infringing your copyright, please provide written notice to our agent listed below for notice of claims of copyright infringement and we will expeditiously remove the allegedly infringing material.

 **DMCA Notification of Claimed Infringement:**  
If you believe that your content has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide us with written notice that includes the following information:

  * Your name, address, telephone number, and email address.
  * A description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed.
  * The URL(s) or a description of where on the yaspan.com service the material you claim is infringing is located.
  * A written statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the use of the copyrighted work is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.
  * A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the information in your notice is accurate, and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf.
  * An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest.

Send your notice to our agent for notices of claimed copyright infringement as follows:

Email: [copyright@yaspan.com](mailto:copyright@yaspan.com)

Postal mail:   
yaspan.com, LLC.  
C/O Saunders & Silverstein, LLP.  
14 Cedar Street - Suite 224    
Amesbury, MA 01913  
Fax: 978.463.9109

 **DMCA Counter-notification:**

  * If you believe your material has been removed in error, please provide us with a written counter-notification that includes the following information:
  * Your name, address, telephone number, and email address.
  * A description of the material that was removed.
  * The URL(s) or a description of where on the yaspan.com service the material appeared prior to removal.
  * A statement under penalty of perjury that you have a good faith belief that the material was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or misidentification.
  * A statement that you consent to the jurisdiction of the Federal District Court for the judicial district in which your address is located, or if your address is outside of the United States, any judicial district in which yaspan.com may be found, and that you will accept service of process from the person who filed the original DMCA notice or an agent of that person.
  * Your electronic or physical signature, or the signature of the person authorized to act on your behalf.

Send your notice to our agent for notices of claimed copyright infringement as follows:

Email: [copyright@yaspan.com](mailto:copyright@yaspan.com)

Postal mail:   
yaspan.com, LLC.  
C/O Saunders & Silverstein, LLP.  
14 Cedar Street - Suite 224    
Amesbury, MA 01913  
Fax: 978.463.9109
